bostondynamics.com 2019-11-08

# Privacy Statement | Boston Dynamics

Boston Dynamics, Inc. (“Boston Dynamics,” “we, “us” or “our”) is committed to safeguarding your online privacy with respect to the information that we obtain from you, or the individual, company or other legal entity that you represent (“you” or “your”) at the Boston Dynamics website located at [www.bostondynamics.com](http://www.bostondynamics.com/), and all associated sites linked to [www.bostondynamics.com](http://www.bostondynamics.com/) by Boston Dynamics, its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, the “Site”). 

Please read this Privacy Statement (“Privacy Statement”) carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how it will be used and protected. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is to refrain from using our Site. By using this Site, you agree to the terms of the most recent version of this Privacy Statement. Please read our Terms of Use, found here, to understand the general rules about your use of this Site. Boston Dynamics may from time to time change this Privacy Statement, so please check back periodically.

Introduction

The information we receive, and how we use it, depends on what you do when visiting our Site. We collect and use your non-personal information (information that is not identifiable to you personally) differently than your personal information.

What is non-personal information?

Non-personal information is information we collect through this Site that does not identify you as an individual person. It may include information such as the following:

  * the type of web browser software you use (for example, Google Chrome)

  * the name of the domain from which you access the Internet

  * the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Site

  * the date and time you access our Site

  * which pages you have visited on our Site 

  * the search terms you use

  * the links on which you click

If you only read or download information on our Site, we do not collect or learn your name, e-mail address, home address, or other personal information about you. We may place a text file called a cookie in the browser files of your computer when you visit our Site. The cookie may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. The information that we collect using cookies is non-personal information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.

What do we do with non-personal information?

Because non-personal information cannot identify you or be tied to you in any way, there are no restrictions on the ways that we can use or share non-personal information. We are always looking for ways to better serve you and improve our Site. We will use non-personal information to help us make this Site more useful to its users. We also will use non-personal information for other business purposes. For example, we may use individual non-personal information or aggregate non-personal information to create reports for internal use to develop programs, products, services or content.

We may use third-party tracking and advertising providers to act on our behalf to track and analyze your usage of our Site through the use of cookies, pixel tags/web beacon, and similar technologies. These third parties may collect, and share with us, as we may request, website usage information about visits to our Site, measure and research the effectiveness of our marketing, and track page usage and paths followed during visits to our Site. Also, these third-party providers may place our Internet banner advertisements on other websites that you visit, and track use of our Internet banner advertisements and other links from our marketing partners’ websites to our Site. The information collected on our behalf by these third parties does not contain your name, address, email address, or any other personally identifiable information.

What is personal information?

Personal information is information we collect through this Site that we can use to specifically identify you, such as your:

  * name

  * email address

  * telephone number

  * IP (Internet Protocol) address when such address is associated with a specific user

In some places on this Site, you have the opportunity to send us personal information about yourself, to elect to receive particular information, or to participate in an activity, such as submitting an invoice. 

How do we keep and use personal information?

We may keep and use personal information we collect from you through this Site to provide you with access to this Site. In addition, we may keep and use your personal information to:

  * respond to your requests

  * contact you with information that might be of interest to you

  * enforce this Privacy Statement and other rules about your use of this Site

  * protect our rights or property

  * comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process

Do we ever share personal information with third parties?

We will not share your personal information collected from this Site with an unrelated third-party without your permission, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Statement.

In the ordinary course of business, we will share some personal information with companies that we hire to perform services or functions on our behalf. In all cases in which we share your personal information with a third-party, we will not authorize them to keep, disclose or use your information with others except for the purpose of providing the requested services. We will not sell, exchange or publish your personal information, except in conjunction with a corporate sale, merger, dissolution, or acquisition.

We may be legally compelled to release your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting visitors to our Site who violate our rules or engage in behavior which is harmful to other visitors (or illegal).

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we feel that the disclosure is necessary to:

  * enforce this Privacy Statement and the other rules about your use of this Site

  * protect our rights or property

  * protect someone’s health, safety or welfare

  * comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process

What happens if the Privacy Statement changes?

If we make changes to this statement, we will update the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this page; however, we encourage you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit the Site. 

What about privacy on other websites?

This Site may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. We provide the links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. This Privacy Statement does not apply to any other website. We are not responsible for the performance of websites operated by third parties or for your business dealings with them. Therefore, whenever you click-through to other websites from this Site we recommend that you review each website’s privacy practices and make your own conclusions regarding the adequacy of these practices.

Do we ever communicate directly with visitors to this Site?

We may contact you periodically by email, mail or telephone if you agree to that contact to provide information regarding programs, products, services and content that may be of interest to you. In addition, some of the features on this Site allow you to communicate with us using an online form. If your communication requests a response from us, we may send you a response via email. The email response or confirmation may include your personal information, including your name, address, etc. We cannot guarantee that our emails to you will be secure from unauthorized interception.

How do you unsubscribe from our contact list?

All email from Boston Dynamics will contain a hyperlink that will allow you to unsubscribe. If, for any reason, you are unable to unsubscribe please contact us in any of the ways listed in the “How to contact Boston Dynamics” section below. 

Are there special rules about children’s privacy?

We care about protecting the online privacy of children. We will not intentionally collect any personal information (such as a child’s name or e-mail address) from children under the age of 18. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 18, please contact [legal@bostondynamics.com](mailto:legal@bostondynamics.com).

What about website security?

Security is very important to us. We also understand that security is important to you. We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, email sent to or from this Site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email.

Applicable Laws

Boston Dynamics is headquartered in the United States of America.  Our use of personal information is subject to applicable US privacy laws.  However, we also comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) with respect to personal information that is collected via our Site.

How do you access, correct, restrict or delete your personal data and object to processing?

You have the right to request access to your personal data, to have your personal data corrected, restricted or deleted, and to object to our processing of your personal data.  You also have the right of data portability, which means that you can request that we provide you (or a third party you designate) with a transferable copy of personal information that you have provided to us.  Your rights may be subject to various limitations under the GDPR. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or if you have any concerns about our processing of your personal data, please contact us in any of the ways listed in the “How to contact Boston Dynamics” section below.

How to contact Boston Dynamics

More information about our Site can be found in our Terms of Use, located here. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement or the practices of our Site, please email us at [legal@bostondynamics.com](mailto:legal@bostondynamics.com) or visit our contact page.

Last Updated on Sep. 18, 2019.
